Associated American Artists
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Artist Files, circa 1958-1980, Series 1:; (Box 1-19; 18.5 linear feet)
  - O'Connor, Thom, (2 folders) (Box 14)
  - O'Donohue, Thomas (Box 14)
  - O'Sullivan, Dennis (Box 14)
  - Ochikubo, Tetsuo, (2 folders) (Box 14)
  - Ockerse, Thomas (Box 14)
  - Oeschger, Ramon E., (2 folders) (Box 14)
  - Oi, Moti (Box 14)
  - Ojeda, Naul (Box 14)
  - Olsen, Dennis (Box 14)
  - Opalkas, Roman (Box 14)
  - Osborne, Elizabeth (Marion Locks Gallery) (Box 14)
  - Ossi, Czinner, (2 folders) (Box 14)
  - Ouchi, Kuniyasu (Box 14)
  - Oudot, Roland (Box 14)
  - Misc. P, (2 folders) (Box 14)
  - Paden, William (Box 14)
  - Paone, Peter, (2 folders) (Box 14)
  - Parker, Whitman J. (Box 14)
  - Parmelee, Terry (Box 14)
  - Patiky, Frances (Box 14)
  - Pearson, Henry (Box 14)
  - Perlmutter, Jack, (2 folders) (Box 14)
  - Perlmutter, Merle (Box 14)
  - Peters, Jurgen, (2 folders) (Box 14)
  - Piddington, H.V. (Box 14)
  - Pierce, Danny (Box 14)
  - Piza, Arthur Luiz, (2 folders) (Box 14)
  - Pla-Narbone, Jose (Box 14)
  - Planten, Henry (Box 14)
  - Plotner, Judith (Box 14)
  - Pohl, Alfred (Box 14)
  - Poleskie, Steve, (2 folders) (Box 14)
  - Ponce de Leon, Michael (Box 14)
  - Pond, Clayton (Box 15)
  - Porter, Ed (Box 15)
  - Porzano, Giacomo (Box 15)
  - Poster, Madeline A. (Box 15)
  - Potin, Jacques, (2 folders) (Box 15)
  - Pozzatti, Rudy, (2 folders) (Box 15)
  - Prado, Nadine (Box 15)
  - Preston, Maggy (Box 15)
  - Pupp, Gisbert (Box 15)
  - Purcell, Roy (Box 15)
  - Pusey, Marvis (Box 15)
  - Putterman, Florence (Box 15)
  - Misc. Q, (2 folders) (Box 15)
  - Misc. R (Box 15)
  - Rabel, (Woolrich) Fanny (Box 15)
  - Rainnie, Felicity (Box 15)
  - Ramsey, Daga (Box 15)
  - Ranth-Ehrenhalt, Ama (Box 15)
  - Raphael, Shirley (Box 15)
  - Rattner, Abraham (Box 15)
  - Reddy, Krishna (Box 15)
  - Reed, Doel (Box 15)
  - Refregier, Anton, (2 folders) (Box 15)
  - Reifel, John Noel (Box 15)
  - Reinhold, Nono, (2 folders) (Box 15)
  - Ret, Etienne, (2 folders) (Box 15)
  - Rethi, Lili, (3 folders) (Box 15)
  - Rheingold, Lois Olian (Box 15)
  - Richards, Rosalyn (Box 15)
  - Rigal, J.J.J., (2 folders) (Box 15)
  - Righi, Federico, (2 folders) (Box 15)
  - Rivera, Xavier (Box 15)
  - Robinson, Alan J. (Box 15)
  - Robinson, Charlotte (Box 15)
  - Rodman, Ruth (Box 15)
  - Rogalski, Walter (Box 15)
  - Roman, Lica, (2 folders) (Box 15)
  - Romano, Umberto, (2 folders) (Box 15)
  - Root, Joan (Box 15)
  - Rosati, Tony (Box 15)
  - Rose, Roslyn (Box 15)
  - Rosenhouse, Irwin (Box 15)
  - Rosenquit, Bernard (Box 15)
  - Rosenthal, Seymour, (2 folders) (Box 15)
  - Ross, Richard (Box 15)
  - Rothe, Gatja H., (2 folders) (Box 15)
  - Rotholz, Rina, (2 folders) (Box 15)
  - Roy, William N. (Box 15)
  - Rubenstein, Lewis, (2 folders) (Box 15)
  - Ruble, Ronald L., (2 folders) (Box 15)
  - Runacher, S. (Box 15)
  - Rush, Andrew, (2 folders) (Box 15)
  - Misc. S, (7 folders) (Box 16)
  - Sachs, Patricia (Box 16)
  - Saito, Kiyoshi, (2 folders) (Box 16)
  - Salinas, Marcel (Box 16)
  - Samberg, Joyce (Box 16)
  - Sanso, Juvenal (Box 16)
  - Sariano, Cornelia Davis (Box 16)
  - Sato, Massaki (Box 16)
  - Sato, Norie (Box 16)
  - Saunier, Hector (Box 16)
  - Savelli, Angelo (Box 16)
  - Schanker, Louis (Box 16)
  - Schary, Emmanuel, (2 folders) (Box 16)
  - Schatsky, Sidney (Box 16)
  - Schiavo, Helen (Box 16)
  - Schreiber, Georges, (2 folders) (Box 16)
  - Schwartz, Aubrey (Box 16)
  - Schwartz, Carl (Box 16)
  - Schwarz, Reiner, (2 folders) (Box 16)
  - Secunda, Arthur (Box 16)
  - Segovia, Andres (Box 16)
  - Seidler, Doris (Box 16)
  - Sexauer, Donald, (2 folders) (Box 16)
  - Sharp, William, (3 folders) (Box 16)
  - Sheilds, Anne Kesler, (2 folders) (Box 16)
  - Siegl, Helen (Box 16)
  - Sills, Joyce (Box 16)
  - Silva, Guillermo (Box 16)
  - Silva, Maria (Box 16)
  - Silverberg, David, (2 folders) (Box 16)
  - Silverberg, Martin (Box 16)
  - Silverman, Mel, (6 folders) (Box 16)
  - Simbari, Nicola (Box 16)
  - Simon, Johanan (Box 16)
  - Singer, Ellen Nathan (Box 16)
  - Singer, Gail (Box 16)
  - Sinisca, Mario, (2 folders) (Box 17)
  - Siporin, Mitchell (Box 17)
  - Sivard, Robert (Box 17)
  - Sloane, Phyllis (Box 17)
  - Small, Blanche (Box 17)
  - Smith, Rosalind (Box 17)
  - Snyder, Toni Goessler (Box 17)
  - Solocheck, Sylvia (Box 17)
  - Sonenberg, Jack (Box 17)
  - Sorelle, Jane (Box 17)
  - Soyer, Moses (Box 17)
  - Soyer, Raphael, (3 folders) (Box 17)
  - Spalatin, Marko (Box 17)
  - Spandorfer, Merle (Box 17)
  - Speck, George, (2 folders) (Box 17)
  - Sperakis, Nicholas (Box 17)
  - Spohn, Marvin, (2 folders) (Box 17)
  - Springer, Ferdinand, (2 folders) (Box 17)
  - Spruance, Benton (Box 17)
  - St. Tamara, Kolba (Box 17)
  - Stack, Frank H., (2 folders) (Box 17)
  - Stasik, Andrew (Box 17)
  - Steffen, Bernard (Box 17)
  - Steg, J.L. (Box 17)
  - Stenzler, Steven (Box 17)
  - Stern, Rosalyn, (2 folders) (Box 17)
  - Stevenson, H. Brockie (Box 17)
  - Stone, Jeffrey Ingram, (2 folders) (Box 17)
  - Stuck, Jack (Box 17)
  - Suggs III, Eldridge, (2 folders) (Box 17)
  - Sullivan, David, (2 folders) (Box 17)
  - Summer, Evan (Box 17)
  - Summers, Carol (Box 17)
  - Suyemura, Keizo (Box 17)
  - Szekessy, Karin, (2 folders) (Box 17)
  - Misc. T, (2 folders) (Box 17)
  - Tabor, Virginia (Box 17)
  - Takal, Peter (Box 17)
  - Talbot, Jonathan (Box 17)
  - Taniguchi, Sigeru, (2 folders) (Box 17)
  - Taplitz, Phyllis, (2 folders) (Box 17)
  - Tarrago, Leticia (Box 17)
  - Taskey, Harry Leroy (Box 17)
  - Taubes, Frederic, (3 folders) (Box 17)
  - Tay, Eng, (2 folders) (Box 17)
  - Taylor, John W. (Box 17)
  - Taylor, Prentiss (Box 17)
  - Tellez, Eugenio (Box 17)
  - Teller, Douglas (Box 17)
  - Tennant, Nancy Chalker (Box 17)
  - Terashi, Katsujiro (Box 17)
  - Tercinet-Levin, Nicole (Box 17)
  - Tetsuya, Noda (Box 17)
  - Thal (Box 17)
  - Thein, John (Box 17)
  - Thevenet, Jacques (Box 17)
  - Thorne, Diane (Box 17)
  - Thornton, Valerie, (2 folders) (Box 18)
  - Thrall, Arthur (Box 18)
  - Tinley, Alan (Box 18)
  - Tmurkian (Box 18)
  - Tobey, Mark (Box 18)
  - Tokita, Ryotaro (Box 18)
  - Toledo, Francisco, (2 folders) (Box 18)
  - Tomasello, Luis (Box 18)
  - Tomchuk, Marjorie (Box 18)
  - Toral, Maria Teresa (Box 18)
  - Tornero, Sergio Gonzalez (Box 18)
  - Torbjorn (Box 18)
  - Tot, Amerigo, (2 folders) (Box 18)
  - Townsend, Lee (Box 18)
  - Trifon, Harriet (Box 18)
  - Trova (Box 18)
  - Trythall, Nona Hershey (Box 18)
  - Tschacbason, Nahum (Box 18)
  - Tsurutani, Noboru, (2 folders) (Box 18)
  - Tumarkin, Igael (Box 18)
  - Tuteur, Jacqueline, (2 folders) (Box 18)
  - Tworkov, Jack (Box 18)
  - Misc. U, (2 folders) (Box 18)
  - Uehling, Judith (Box 18)
  - Umana, A. (Box 18)
  - Utpatel, Frank (Box 18)
  - Urs, F. Studer (Box 18)
  - Misc. V (Box 18)
  - Vaccino, Alyce King (Box 18)
  - Valier, Biron, (2 folders) (Box 18)
  - Vallade, Fred (Box 18)
  - Valtchev, Ivan (Box 18)
  - Van De Velde, Jan (Box 18)
  - Van Leyden, Lucas (Box 18)
  - Van Nimwegen, D. (Box 18)
  - Van Rossem, Ru (Box 18)
  - Van Suchtelen, Adrian (Box 18)
  - Van Veen, Stuyvesant, (2 folders) (Box 18)
  - Vanni, Giovanni Battista (Box 18)
  - Vaughn, Jeffrey L. (Box 18)
  - Vaux, Marc (Box 18)
  - Veldhoen, A.J. (Box 18)
  - Velonis, Anthony (Box 18)
  - Veret, Corinne (Box 18)
  - Vernunft, Verena (Box 18)
  - Vertez, Dora (Box 18)
  - Vespignani, Renzo (Box 18)
  - Victor, Martine (Box 18)
  - Vieillard, Roger, (2 folders) (Box 18)
  - Viera, Ricardo (Box 18)
  - Viesulas, Romas, (2 folders) (Box 18)
  - Vilchis, Fernando (Box 18)
  - Virgil (Box 18)
  - Virgona, Hank (Box 18)
  - Van Hoesen, Beth, (2 folders) (Box 18)
  - Van Vliet, Claire, (2 folders) (Box 18)
  - Vivell, Judith (Box 18)
  - Vodvarka, Frank (Box 18)
  - Von Hentig, Urd (Box 18)
  - Von Wicht, John, (3 folders) (Box 18)
  - Misc. W, (3 folders) (Box 18)
  - Wada, Steve, (2 folders) (Box 18)
  - Wagner, G. Noble (Box 18)
  - Wakata, Akira, (2 folders) (Box 18)
  - Wakita, Aijiro (Box 18)
  - Wales, George C. (Box 18)
  - Wales, Shirley, (2 folders) (Box 18)
  - Walker, Kenneth H., (2 folders) (Box 18)
  - Wallace, Beverly (Box 18)
  - Walsh, Alexander Dewitt (Box 18)
  - Waters, Margaret (Box 18)
  - Walters, Sylvia (Box 18)
  - Wasserman, Burton (Box 18)
  - Weddige, Emil, (2 folders) (Box 18)
  - Weege, William (Box 18)
  - Weisbuch, Claude (Box 18)
  - Wells, Kappy (Box 18)
  - Westerman, H.C. (Box 18)
  - Westring, Mary (Box 18)
  - Wiles, Irving Ramsey (Box 18)
  - Wilkinson, Donald (Box 18)
  - Williams, Joan (Box 18)
  - Wilson, Charles (Box 18)
  - Wilson, Sol (Box 19)
  - Winick, Lisa Mona Frances (Box 19)
  - Winkelman, Joseph (Box 19)
  - Woiceske, Ronau William (Box 19)
  - Wolchonok, Louis (Box 19)
  - Wolf, Arne, (2 folders) (Box 19)
  - Wolf, Ben, (2 folders) (Box 19)
  - Wolf, Helen (Box 19)
  - Wolfson, William (Box 19)
  - Wunderlich, Paul (Box 19)
  - Wygonik, William T. (Box 19)
  - Ximenez, Alfredo (Box 19)
  - Misc. Y (Box 19)
  - Misc. Y - Z (Box 19)
  - Yamin, Steven B. (Box 19)
  - Yarbrough, Leila (Box 19)
  - Yarinsky, Estelle (Box 19)
  - Yeargans, Hartwell (Box 19)
  - Yokoi, Tomoe (Box 19)
  - Yoong, Bae (Box 19)
  - Yoshida, Hiroshi (Box 19)
  - Yoshida, Toshi (Box 19)
  - Yoshihara, Hideo (Box 19)
  - Youkeles, Anne (Box 19)
  - Youngblood, Judy (Box 19)
  - Youngerman, Jack (Box 19)
  - Yunkers, Adja (Box 19)
  - Yvaral, Jean Pierre (Box 19)
  - Misc. Z (Box 19)
  - Zabar, Abbie (Box 19)
  - Zadkine, Ossip (Box 19)
  - Zalce, Alfredo (Box 19)
  - Zao-Wou-Ki (Box 19)
  - Zeitlin, Harriet (Box 19)
  - Zetterholm, Torbjorn (Box 19)
  - Zimiles, Murray (Box 19)
  - Zinkel, Barbara (Box 19)
  - Zoellner, Richard (Box 19)
  - Zorach, William (Box 19)
  - Misc. Photos of Artists, (2 folders) (Box 19)
  - Misc. Photographs and Slides of Works of Art (Box 19)
  - Misc. Printed Material (Box 19)
- Dealers, Galleries and Museums, circa 1958-1980, Series 2:; (Box 19-29; 10.5 linear feet)
  - A-Z, Misc. (Box 19)
  - A, Misc. (Box 19)
  - A.C. Mazo (Box 19)
  - Adria Art Inc. (Box 19)
  - A+G De May (Box 19)
  - Alberto Caprini (Box 19)
  - Albright-Knox Art Gallery, (2 folders) (Box 19)
  - Allan Frumkin Gallery Inc. (Box 19)
  - American Color Print Society (Box 19)
  - American Express (Box 19)
  - Anderson's (Minnesota) (Box 19)
  - Angus Whyte Gallery (Box 19)
  - Antares (Box 19)
  - Armory 50th Anniversary Show - Henry St. Settlement (Box 19)
  - Arnot Art Gallery Ass'n (Box 19)
  - Arta (Box 19)
  - Art Center Studio and Gallery, Inc. (Box 19)
  - Art Fair, Washington International (Box 19)
  - Art Gallery of Clearwater (Box 19)
  - Art Harris Art Gallery (Box 19)
  - Art In The Embassies (Box 19)
  - Art Originals Gallery (Box 19)
  - Art Reference Gallery Inc. (Box 20)
  - Art Supply Center (Box 20)
  - Atelier Lacouriere et Frelaut - Ateliers Int'l (Box 20)
  - B, Misc. (Box 20)
  - Barre Publishing Co. (Box 20)
  - Bates College (Box 20)
  - Berman-Medalie Gallery, Inc. (Box 20)
  - Bernard Colson (Box 20)
  - Bezalel National Museum (Box 20)
  - Birmingham Museum of Art (Box 20)
  - Black Hawk College (Box 20)
  - Boscov's (Box 20)
  - Brigitte Eitingon, Fine Arts, Ltd. (Box 20)
  - Brusberg, Dieter (Brusberg Galerie), (6 folders) (Box 20)
  - Bucknell University (Box 20)
  - C, Misc. (Box 20)
  - Casdin Gallery (Box 20)
  - C.F.A. Graphics (Box 20)
  - Childs Gallery - Christie's (Box 20)
  - Christopher Mendez (Box 20)
  - Ciranna Gallery (Box 20)
  - Circle Fine Art (Box 20)
  - Cirrus Editions Ltd. (Box 20)
  - Cober Gallery (Box 20)
  - Collectors Guild (Box 20)
  - Collectors Press (Box 20)
  - Cornell Art Tour (Box 20)
  - Cornell University, (4 folders) (Box 20)
  - Cushing Galleries (Box 20)
  - Custom Art (Box 20)
  - D, Misc. (Box 20)
  - Dayton's Gallery (Box 21)
  - Denison University (Box 21)
  - Depauw University (Box 21)
  - Doane College (Box 21)
  - Dominion Gallery (Box 21)
  - Downtown Gallery (Box 21)
  - Drew University (Box 21)
  - Drexel Institute of Technology (Box 21)
  - Dutchess Community College (Box 21)
  - E, Misc. (Box 21)
  - Edgemont Fine Galleries (Box 21)
  - Ediciones Poligrafa/SA (Box 21)
  - Edith Halpert (Estate) (Box 21)
  - Edition Domberger - Edition Monica Beck (Box 21)
  - Editions Alecto Limited - Editions Limited Gallery (Box 21)
  - Editions Denise Rene (Box 21)
  - Edward Weston Graphics (Box 21)
  - Elaine Mittelman (Interiors) (Box 21)
  - Erker Galerie/Erker Presse (Box 21)
  - Eva Thoby-Marcelin (Box 21)
  - F, Misc. (Box 21)
  - Far Gallery (Box 21)
  - Felicie, Inc. (Box 21)
  - Felix Landau Gallery (Box 21)
  - Fine Arts 260 (Box 21)
  - Fine Prints, Ltd. - Fstop, Ltd., Inc. (Box 21)
  - Flair Gallery (Box 21)
  - Frank J. Oehlschlaeger (Box 21)
  - Franklin Mint (Box 21)
  - Frederick Chusid and Co. (Box 21)
  - Frederick Mulder (Box 21)
  - G, Misc. (Box 21)
  - Galeria de Antonio Souza (Box 21)
  - Galeria Ciranna - Galeria Colibri (Box 21)
  - Galerie Alain Digard - Galerie Paul Vallotton (Box 21)
  - Galerie Schindler (Box 22)
  - Galerie Schmucking (Box 22)
  - Galerie Stubler - Galerie Wendelin (Box 22)
  - Galerie Wilbrand - Galerie Wolfgang Ketterer (Box 22)
  - Gallery Grefalt (Box 22)
  - Gallery of Modern Art (Box 22)
  - Gallery Murakami (Box 22)
  - Gallery 100 (Box 22)
  - Gallery 121 (Box 22)
  - Gallery R.G. (Curacao) (Box 22)
  - Gemini G.E.L. (Box 22)
  - George Braziller Inc. (Box 22)
  - George Washington University (Box 22)
  - Ginger Davis (Box 22)
  - Giraffe Gallery (Box 22)
  - Gordon College (Box 22)
  - Graphic Guild (Guilde Graphique) (Box 22)
  - Graphics Collectors Consortium, Inc. (Box 22)
  - Gropper Art Gallery (Box 22)
  - H, Misc. (Box 22)
  - Hanover Gallery (Box 22)
  - Henry J. Planten (Box 22)
  - Herboche, (2 folders) (Box 22)
  - Hillsdale Board of Education (Box 22)
  - Huntington Gallery (Box 22)
  - I, Misc. (Box 22)
  - Il Bisonte (Box 22)
  - Il Torcoliere (Box 22)
  - International Art Associates, Ltd. (Box 22)
  - International Graphic Arts Society (Box 22)
  - J, Misc. (Box 22)
  - Jacksonville Art Museum (Box 22)
  - Jacques M. Frapier, (3 folders) (Box 22)
  - J.L. Hudson Gallery (Box 22)
  - J. Thomas Gallery (Box 22)
  - Judson College (Box 23)
  - K, Misc. (Box 23)
  - Kalamazoo Institute, (2 folders) (Box 23)
  - Kansas University Union Bookstore (Box 23)
  - Karl Moulder (Box 23)
  - Kraushaar Galleries (Box 23)
  - L, Misc. (Box 23)
  - Landfall Press (Box 23)
  - Lasalle and Koch (Box 23)
  - L'Estampe Originale (Box 23)
  - Library of Congress, (3 folders) (Box 23)
  - Libreria Marsilio da Padova Galleria (Box 23)
  - Light (Box 23)
  - Limited Editions Club (Box 23)
  - Lola Nirenberg (Box 23)
  - L'Ouevre Gravee, (3 folders) (Box 23)
  - M, Misc. (Box 23)
  - Makler Gallery (Box 23)
  - Malmo Museum (Box 23)
  - Mark J. Sandler, (2 folders) (Box 23)
  - Marlborough Graphics, (2 folders) (Box 24)
  - Martha Jackson Graphics (Box 24)
  - Martin Gordon Gallery (Box 24)
  - Martin Lawrence Limited Editions (Box 24)
  - Mason Fine Prints (Box 24)
  - McCann Wood Gallery (Box 24)
  - Merrill Chase (Box 24)
  - Merryman Collection (Box 24)
  - Mickelson's Gallery (Box 24)
  - Middendorf Gallery (Box 24)
  - M.I.T. (Box 24)
  - Mixed Media Gallery (Box 24)
  - Molton Gallery (Box 24)
  - Morris Louis Appelman (Box 24)
  - Muggleton Gallery (Box 24)
  - Multiples, Inc. (Box 24)
  - Museo La Tertulia - Museo de Bellas Artes de Caracas (Box 24)
  - Museum of Graphic Art (Box 24)
  - Museum of Modern Art, (5 folders) (Box 24)
  - N, Misc., (2 folders) (Box 24)
  - Nahan Galleries (Box 24)
  - Nantenshi Gallery (Box 24)
  - National Academy of Design (Box 24)
  - New Gallery (Box 25)
  - New York Graphic Society (Box 25)
  - Nierendorf Galerie (Box 25)
  - Nouvelle Images (M. Blanc) (Box 25)
  - O, Misc., (2 folders) (Box 25)
  - Oeuvres Graphiques (Box 25)
  - One Art Service (Box 25)
  - Orangerie Verlag (Box 25)
  - Original Print Collectors Group, Ltd. (Box 25)
  - Original Prints Art (Box 25)
  - Original Prints Gallery (Box 25)
  - Oxford Gallery (Box 25)
  - P, Misc., (2 folders) (Box 25)
  - Pennsylvania Academy of Fine Arts - Penta (Box 25)
  - Pace Editions, Inc. (Box 25)
  - Pallas Gallery (Box 25)
  - Panek Gallery (Box 25)
  - Parasol Press, Ltd. (Box 25)
  - Pasadena Art Museum (Box 25)
  - Parke Bernet, (2 folders) (Box 25)
  - Parke Bernet - N.Y., (4 folders) (Box 25)
  - Parke Bernet - L.A., (2 folders) (Box 26)
  - Parke Bernet - Paul Gallery (Box 26)
  - Paul McCarron Fine Prints (Box 26)
  - Peggy Christian (Box 26)
  - Petersburg Press (Box 26)
  - Philadelphia Art Alliance - Philadephia Museum of Art (Box 26)
  - Phoenix Gallery (Box 26)
  - Pratt Graphic Art Center, (2 folders) (Box 26)
  - Premier Gallery, Inc. (Box 26)
  - Print Art Center (Box 26)
  - Print Council of America, (2 folders) (Box 26)
  - Print Trader (Box 26)
  - Provincetown Art Association (Box 26)
  - Publinel (Box 26)
  - Pyramid Arts, Ltd (Box 26)
  - Q, Misc. (Box 26)
  - R, Misc. (Box 26)
  - Ramscale Graphics (Box 26)
  - R.E. Lewis, Inc. (Box 26)
  - R.E. Lewis Original Prints and Drawings (Box 26)
  - Rene Breheret (Box 26)
  - Retina Gallery (Box 26)
  - R.G. Michel, (2 folders) (Box 26)
  - Rijksakademi (Box 26)
  - Roger Reinke (Box 26)
  - Roger Trlak (Box 27)
  - Ronnie Brenner Gallery (Box 27)
  - S, Misc. (Box 27)
  - S.A.G.A. (Society of American Graphic Artists), (3 folders) (Box 27)
  - School of Paris Graphics (Box 27)
  - School of Visual Arts (Box 27)
  - Select Arts Society, (2 folders) (Box 27)
  - Sheldon Swope Art Gallery (Box 27)
  - Shorewood Graphic Workshop (Box 27)
  - Simmons College (Box 27)
  - Sporrong Grafikab (Box 27)
  - St. Lawrence University (Box 27)
  - St. Paul Art Center (Box 27)
  - Stanley William Hayter (Box 27)
  - State University, Oswego (Box 27)
  - Sylvia Sherman (Box 27)
  - Syracuse University (Box 27)
  - Szoke Graphics (John Szoke) (Box 27)
  - T, Misc. (Box 27)
  - Tamarind Lithography Workshop, (3 folders) (Box 27)
  - Temple Beth El (Box 27)
  - Theodore B. Donson Ltd. (Box 27)
  - Toho Bijutu Boeki Co. (Box 28)
  - Transworld Art (Box 28)
  - Trois Anges, Ltd. (Box 28)
  - Tyler Graphics Ltd. (Box 28)
  - U, Misc. (Box 28)
  - University of California - University of Southern Illinois (Box 28)
  - University of Glasgow - Grosvenor Gallery (Box 28)
  - University of Maine, (4 folders) (Box 28)
  - University of Oklahoma (Box 28)
  - University of Southern Florida (Box 28)
  - University of Washington (Box 28)
  - U.S.I.A., (1, 2, 3 of 4 folders) (Box 28)
  - U.S.I.A., (4 of 4 folders) (Box 29)
  - U.S. Naval Air Station (Box 29)
  - V, Misc. (Box 29)
  - Victoria and Albert Museum (Box 29)
  - Village Bazaar Inc. (Box 29)
  - W, Misc. (Box 29)
  - Weinreb and Douwma, Ltd. (Box 29)
  - Western Illinois University (Box 29)
  - William B. Curran and Associates (Box 29)
  - Witte Memorial Museum (Box 29)
  - Woodward Foundation (Box 29)
  - World Graphics (Box 29)
  - Y-Z, Misc. (Box 29)
- Client Files, circa 1958-1980, Series 3:; (Box 29-48; 19 linear feet)
  - Aa-Al (Box 29)
  - Am-Ar (Box 29)
  - As-Az (Box 29)
  - Baa-Bad (Box 29)
  - Bae-Bar (Box 29)
  - Bas-Baz (Box 29)
  - Bea-Bec (Box 29)
  - Bee-Benj (Box 29)
  - Beno-Berg (Box 29)
  - Berk-Bern (Box 29)
  - Berr-Bez (Box 29)
  - Bi-Boo, (5 folders) (Box 29)
  - Bor, (3 folders) (Box 30)
  - Bra-Bro, (4 folders) (Box 30)
  - Booker, William P. (Box 30)
  - Brown, James C., (2 folders) (Box 30)
  - Brown, Robert (Box 30)
  - Bru-Bz, (3 folders) (Box 30)
  - Benoliel, Peter A. (Box 30)
  - Caa-Caq (Box 30)
  - Car-Chas, (2 folders) (Box 30)
  - Carr, Gene (Box 30)
  - Chapman, J. Leo (Box 30)
  - Che-Ci (Box 30)
  - Cao-Com, (4 folders) (Box 30)
  - Con-Cop, (2 folders) (Box 30)
  - Condit, Marian (Box 31)
  - Cor-Cz, (3 folders) (Box 31)
  - Da, (3 folders) (Box 31)
  - Dav, (2 folders) (Box 31)
  - Dunnegan, T.H.B. (Box 31)
  - De (Box 31)
  - Den, (2 folders) (Box 31)
  - Di, (2 folders) (Box 31)
  - Doa, (3 folders) (Box 31)
  - Doo, (2 folders) (Box 31)
  - Dun-Dz, (2 folders) (Box 31)
  - Ea-Eh, (1 of 2 folders) (Box 31)
  - Ea-Eh, (2 of 2 folders) (Box 32)
  - Ei-Ez, (3 folders) (Box 32)
  - Er-Ez, (3 folders) (Box 32)
  - Fab-Far, (3 folders) (Box 32)
  - Far-Faz (Box 32)
  - French, Robert L. (Box 32)
  - Fe, (2 folders) (Box 32)
  - Fi-Fil, (2 folders) (Box 32)
  - Fir-Fiz, (2 folders) (Box 32)
  - Fl-Fo, (1 of 2 folders) (Box 32)
  - Fl-Fo, (2 of 2 folders) (Box 33)
  - Fra-Fri, (3 folders) (Box 33)
  - Fro (Box 33)
  - Gab-Gan (Box 33)
  - Gar-Gh, (2 folders) (Box 33)
  - Gia-Gil, (3 folders) (Box 33)
  - Gla-Glu, (3 folders) (Box 33)
  - God-Goldm, (3 folders) (Box 33)
  - Godfrey, Gaston O. (Box 33)
  - Goldn-Gray, (4 folders) (Box 33)
  - Goodfellow, William D. (Box 34)
  - Gor-Gree, (2 folders) (Box 34)
  - Gray, Walter (Box 34)
  - Greg-Gz, (3 folders) (Box 34)
  - Haa-Hal (Box 34)
  - Hagge, Robert S. (Box 34)
  - Ham-Hard, (3 folders) (Box 34)
  - Hare-Harz, (3 folders) (Box 34)
  - Has-Haz, (2 folders) (Box 34)
  - Hea-Hin, (1, 2 of 4 folders) (Box 34)
  - Hea-Hin, (3, 4 of 4 folders) (Box 35)
  - Hir-Hol, (3 folders) (Box 35)
  - Hol-Hot, (3 folders) (Box 35)
  - Horowitz, Harold (Box 35)
  - Hoselitz, Bert F. (Box 35)
  - Hou-Hun, (3 folders) (Box 35)
  - Hur-Hz, (2 folders) (Box 35)
  - I, (2 folders) (Box 35)
  - Ja, (3 folders) (Box 35)
  - Jb-John, (3 folders) (Box 35)
  - Jor-Jz, (3 folders) (Box 36)
  - Ka, (3 folders) (Box 36)
  - Kar-Kaz, (2 folders) (Box 36)
  - Kelchak, Joseph (Box 36)
  - Kel-Kem, (4 Folders) (Box 36)
  - Ki, (3 folders) (Box 36)
  - Kl, (3 folders) (Box 36)
  - Kn-Kr, (3 folders) (Box 36)
  - Kre-Krz, (3 folders) (Box 37)
  - Ku-Kz, (2 folders) (Box 37)
  - La-Lar, (4 folders) (Box 37)
  - Las-Laz, (3 folders) (Box 37)
  - Lea-Lef, (3 folders) (Box 37)
  - Leeds, Patricia (Box 37)
  - Leg-Les, (2 folders) (Box 37)
  - Leve-Levins, (2 folders) (Box 37)
  - Levit-Lez, (2 folders) (Box 37)
  - Li, (2 folders) (Box 37)
  - Lin-Lm, (3 folders) (Box 37)
  - Lo-Lt, (3 folders) (Box 38)
  - Lu, (3 folders) (Box 38)
  - Lyss, Stan (Box 38)
  - Ma, (2 folders) (Box 38)
  - Mac A-Mac Z, (2 folders) (Box 38)
  - Mai, (2 folders) (Box 38)
  - Man, (2 folders) (Box 38)
  - Mar, (2 folders) (Box 38)
  - Marr-Mart, (2 folders) (Box 38)
  - Mas-Mats, (2 folders) (Box 38)
  - Matsuda, Yukio (Box 38)
  - Matt-Maz, (3 folders) (Box 38)
  - Mc E-Mc I, (2 folders) (Box 39)
  - McClain, Tom G. (Box 39)
  - Mc K-Mc Z, (2 folders) (Box 39)
  - Mc Laughlin, Fr. Thomas (Box 39)
  - Mea-Men, (3 folders) (Box 39)
  - Mer-Mez, (2 folders) (Box 39)
  - Mich (Box 39)
  - Mick-Mil (Box 39)
  - Miller, (3 folders) (Box 39)
  - Milli-Miz, (3 folders) (Box 39)
  - Mills, Milton (Box 39)
  - Mob-Morg, (3 folders) (Box 39)
  - Morr-Mort, (2 folders) (Box 39)
  - Mos-Mura, (1 of 2 folders) (Box 39)
  - Mos-Mura, (2 of 2 folders) (Box 40)
  - Murphy-Mz (Box 40)
  - Na-Nez, (3 folders) (Box 40)
  - Ni-Nz, (2 folders) (Box 40)
  - Norgress, Ben C. (Box 40)
  - O-On, (2 folders) (Box 40)
  - Oderberg, Phil (Box 40)
  - Op-Oz, (2 folders) (Box 40)
  - Pac, (2 folders) (Box 40)
  - Pappajohn, John (Box 40)
  - Park-Paz, (2 folders) (Box 40)
  - Pea-Perkins, (1, 2, 3, of 4 folders) (Box 40)
  - Pea-Perkins, (4 of 4 folders) (Box 41)
  - Penney, Charles R. (Box 41)
  - Perl-Pf, (4 folders) (Box 41)
  - Ph-Piz, (3 folders) (Box 41)
  - Pl-Pon, (3 folders) (Box 41)
  - Poo-Pre, (3 folders) (Box 41)
  - Pri-Q, (2 folders) (Box 41)
  - Ra-Rao, (3 folders) (Box 41)
  - Ramer, Dr. Barry S. (Box 41)
  - Rap-Reed, (2 folders) (Box 41)
  - Rawson, Clifford S. (Box 41)
  - Rees-Reis, (2 folders) (Box 42)
  - Regan, Lawrence (Box 42)
  - Reit-Rif, (2 folders) (Box 42)
  - Rig-Robertson, (2 folders) (Box 42)
  - Robins-Rol, (2 folders) (Box 42)
  - Rodney, Dr. Marvin (Box 42)
  - Rom-Ross, (2 folders) (Box 42)
  - Rost-Roz, (2 folders) (Box 42)
  - Rua-Rup, (2 folders) (Box 42)